urbanhomez.com 2018-09-29

# 

**Valion Infosystems Pvt. Ltd.** {hereinafter referred to as " **Valion** "} is committed to safeguarding its Users privacy. We request all our Users to read the following **'Privacy Policy** ' to understand how their personal & business information will be treated, as they make full use of our services to their benefit.

In general, a User can visit UrbanHomez.com web pages without providing or revealing any Personal or Business Information about themselves.

**Your Consent  **

By using this UrbanHomez.com Marketplace, the User consents to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Valion’s processing of Personal & Business Information for the purposes given below.

**Collection of Information**

Valion collects information from its users when they register to gain access to our services or at other specific instances when they are requested to provide us with their personal & business information. During registration, we ask the users for their name, email address, Mobile number, business information and other personal details. Once a user registers, he/she is no longer anonymous to Valion and it is deemed that the user has given Valion the right to publish the desired business & personal details throughout its marketplace/s, including but not limited to, business directory, enquiry, catalogs etc.

When you are on our network and are asked for personal information, you are sharing the information with Valion alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Promotions that run on our network may be sponsored by companies other than Valion or may be co-sponsored by Valion and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. However, you can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared.

We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, browser software, screen resolution etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services.

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.

**Use of Personal & Business Information**

Valion’s primary goal in collecting personal or public information is to provide the user with a customized experience on our network of sites. This includes personalized services, interactive communication and other services, some of which are completely free and remaining are paid. Business information is used to display the user's business listing or product offerings across our network to fetch maximum business opportunities for the user.

In order to provide free services, Valion displays advertisements based upon the site usage statistics and visitor trends. Valion uses user's personal & business information to serve targeted advertisements through its websites, newsletters and customized mailers. In addition to it, once the user's personal and business information is displayed on our network, the user may start receiving business enquiries through email, phone or normal mail, from various buyers and sellers that might or might not be of their interest. Valion does not exercise any control over its users for sending business enquiries to the listed members.

**Sharing of Information**

As a general rule, Valion will not disclose or share any of the user's personally identifiable information except when Valion has the user's permission or under special circumstances, such as when Valion believes in good faith that the law requires it or as permitted in terms of this policy.

Valion may also disclose account information in special cases when Valion has reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Valion's Terms of Services or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Valion's rights or property, other Valion network website users, or if Valion deems it necessary to maintain, service, and improve its products and services. Personal information collected may be transferred and shared in the event of a sale.

**Distribution of Information**

Valion may, from time to time, send its users emails regarding its products and services. Valion constantly tries and improves the marketplace products/services for better efficiency, more relevancy, innovative business matchmaking and better personal preferences. Valion has many products/services on the marketplace to be used by its users for making relevant business contacts with each other.  Valion may send or allow to be sent direct mails with respect/pertaining to the products and services of third parties that it feels may be of interest to the user or if the user has shown interest in your company for business requirement by way of our paid buyers-sellers contact services. Only Valion, its registered members or its agents working under confidentiality agreements will send these direct mailers. Relevancy of the contacts made between users would depend upon the information sought & given by various users.

**Protection of information**

As with all information, Valion does not sell any data in bulk to third party that can be misused for telemarketing or bulk mailing or any other wrong purposes. In addition, Valion does not sell any user's personal information or business information until and unless it is permitted by the user. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding product or service usage on Valion network is provided in an aggregate form only and does not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. 

We request our users to sign out of their  _<http://www.urbanhomez.com/>_  account and close their browser window when they have finished their work. This is to ensure that others cannot access their personal or business information and correspondence, if the user shares the computer with someone else or is using a computer in a public place.

Valion takes necessary steps, within its limits of commercial viability and necessity, to ensure that the user's information is treated securely.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Valion strives to protect the user's personal & business information, it cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to Valion and you do so at your own risk. Once Valion receives your transmission, it makes best efforts to ensure its security in its systems. Please keep in mind that whenever you post personal & business information online, that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

**Third Party Services**

Third parties provide certain services available on http://www.urbanhomez.com/ on Valion’s behalf. Valion may provide information, including Personal & Business Information of Users/Members that Valion collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Valion maintains its Web site and mailing lists. Valion will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Valion’s behalf.

Valion does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Valion’s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Valion’s policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

**Disclaimer**

Valion does not store or keep credit card data with itself. 

Valion shall not be liable for any loss or damage sustained by reason of any disclosure (inadvertent or otherwise) of any information concerning the user's account and / or information shared by the user with Valion.

**Comments**

Valion welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this ‘Privacy Policy’, Valion will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically.
